This is wiseman Harry
moving in the midst of those who have come to the Synagogue Church of all Nations
in search of Divine intervention to bring solution,
deliverance and all of God's
blessings to their life.
The power of God works in
the Spirit setting captives free.
What you are watching is the reality
that Jesus Christ lives, He never said goodbye.
And He has made a way for us to be separated
from the darkness behind every
adversity in life.
Let's watch as all the shades of darkness are dispelled
from this young man's life in the
mighty
name of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.
Who are you?
Huh?
Why do you want to know?
What have you done to him?
I have destroyed his education.
Who are you inside of him?
I am an idol.
You are an idol.
What have you done to his family?
There is no prosperity in his family.
Who removed the prosperity?
I am the one.
You are the one.
Why did you destroy his education?
He is at the university,
I made him drink alcohol.
I make him drink, he can take a
packet of cigarettes in 30 minutes.
Within 30 minutes?
Yes.
Three packets?
Yes!
Why did you make that to him?
That makes me happy.
That makes you happy?
Yes!
Okay, how do you normally operate in his life?
I operate through dreams.
Through dreams?
Yes.
How?
I sleep with him in dreams.
Out! In the name of Jesus.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In Jesus' name.
In Jesus' name, thank you Lord!
You are free in the name of Jesus.
How are you?
I am good.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
So Jesus Christ has delivered you.
Thank you, Jesus, I'm free.
You are free!
I am Mr Jesse Delali.
I'm from Ghana.
My testimony goes like this.
I've lived 21 years of my life for the devil.
This whole thing started when I was
8 years old,
I was taken to my grandmother's
hometown for a funeral
after which I saw the way my
people were worshipping idols.
So I was kind of enticed and got interested in it.
So I got closer to that place and then
looked at the way they were
kind of performing the rituals.
After that, that day I went home,
and then I just developed
a habit of stealing.
Okay, before you go ahead,
can you just tell us the home you brought up in
and the type of background you are from?
I was brought up from a very strict Christian home.
My dad was very strict and academician
and my mum was also very prayerful.
Yeah, that was the kind of home I was brought up in.
So you're brought up in a strict Christian home
but when you were eight years old
you went to the village for a funeral.
And tell us exactly what happened,
when you went to that funeral.
What did you see there?
When I went for the funeral, I
realized that my dad's home, his family -
they were idol worshippers.
So they would use their mouth to
bite the head of a live chicken.
So I got interested in it
and I got closer to see how
they were performing their rituals.
So as a small boy, you were just
watching closely as they were performing
this ritual and then what happened to you?
From that day, I came home and then I just developed
the habit of picking stuffs from the house.
So from that age of eight as
you returned from this funeral
you began to steal?
Yeah.
Okay, can you just tell us more
about how this developed
and how serious this spirit
of stealing became?
This thing developed from
stage to stage as a young guy.
I could go into my parents
room and steal their money.
It got to a time, because of
this stealing habits,
I took it from home to outside.
I started taking things from my friends.
I easily made friends - when I
got to a place I would make friends.
I ended up taking stuff from them.
Because of this thing, I was expelled
from about two junior high schools
before I went to senior high school.
And when I went to senior high school,
I was still in this mess.
I went to the university and I met friends
who were spending money.
So I asked them how they
made their money.
So before you go to that level, tell us for example
the type of things you would steal and how
you would go about stealing those items
anytime that spirit of stealing came into you?
I would steal money - money was the thing
I would steal most of the time.
I would enter room; I won't be
there when they hide the money.
But I could enter the room, sit down
and I could smell the money in that room.
I needed the money, I would close my eyes
for two minutes and open my eyes.
I would just move straight to
where the money was kept.
And l would just pick it.
So even if that money is hidden in a very secret place,
once you entered the room and
closed your eyes -
a spirit would push you to
know where that money is located?
Yeah.
How much money were you
stealing on a regular basis?
I was stealing thousands of dollars.
I was stealing money, I was into
stealing money from my home.
And what were you using this
money to do,
what were you using this money for?
I would go and buy good stuff for myself,
I would buy shoes and shirts.
Okay, so we are hearing from our brother
he is explaining how from the age of 8,
he began to develop a habit of stealing after
he went to funeral where he witnessed
idol worship and a specific ritual being performed.
And he said, anytime he used to go
into a room to steal,
a spirit would communicate to him
where that money was located and he would be able to steal.
He has stolen thousands of dollars,
and he would just use this money to live a very lavish
lifestyle - flamboyant lifestyle.
So tell us, as you got older, how did this develop
and become even more serious?
This became serious when I got to university;
when I got to university, I met friends who were spending money,
they were living kind of big life.
So with the kind of money that I was
getting from home was not enough,
since my dad was very strict;
he started restricting me.
So I asked them how they made their money,
and then I was introduced to how they got their money.
Initially they did not want to tell me,
but upon several pressurization
I was introduced to how they made their money;
which I also got enticed into it,
and I started getting my money.
It involved spiritualist.
Firstly, and I was given a spiritualist number
that I called on phone, and I told
him I needed money.
So he gave me some options which I chose one
out of the numerous options
he gave me.
Which I went in for.
He gave me several options. Some of the options were like
'wallet money', 'instant money', 'god's money', 'bank's money' and 'do as I say'.
With the 'wallet money' for instance, in my country,
the biggest currency we use is 50 Ghana cedis.
Now you would send an empty
wallet to the spiritualist.
When you send the wallet to him,
he will command the 50 cedis into your wallet.
That 50 cedis you can use to buy a car,
you can use to buy a house,
you can use to buy anything you want to.
It works this way.
You go out there and use the 50 cedis
to purchase something from a store.
Now, when you use that money to
buy something from the store -
let's say you buy something like 5 Cedis out of it -
and change will be given to you.
When that change is given to you,
you'll keep that change separately from where the wallet is.
You put your wallet back into your pocket.
30 seconds after the money you
used to purchase
something from the store,
the money would come back into your wallet.
So depending on the number
of stores you go within a day,
that will determine the amount
of money you get within day.
Brethren, if you are not a good Christian
or someone who prays,
and that money will mix with your money...
Let's say you are a trader, and if
that money mixes with your money -
within six months your money will go to the drain,
and you won't be able to account for anything.
That was the first option.
Okay, now before going ahead
when you went to
this spiritualist to involve yourself
and these money rituals -
what were the conditions laid down,
what were the things he asked you to bring
and the conditions that were laid down
before he went ahead to do
these specific money rituals?
When you call them on phone,
initially, they will tell you: "No blood" -
they don't need blood from you.
So when you go to them, they would ask you
to bring an amount of money
which you will use to go and buy
some stuff from the market.
And he would tell you that he
was going to call your star.
If your star responds, that will determine
the amount of money they are going to get.
First, I was asked to bring an
amount of money which I sent
and they used it to buy certain
things from the market.
And then he called my star,
my star came,
and then he asked me the
amount of money that I wanted.
My amount options was actually 'instant money'.
So he poured powder in my hand and
asked me how much money I needed.
And I mentioned the amount that I needed.
Then he did some things for about 20 minutes
and he opened a box and the
money was in the box.
The exact amount I was looking
for was in the box.
So, I took it to campus and started spending it.
It got to a time I flattered the whole office,
and then he asked me to bring human blood.
I told him that I wasn't doing it,
in fact I called him on phone and insulted him.
And then I moved to a different spiritualist.
So you said that initially they told you that
you would not require blood.
But once you had used this ritual
and obtained instant money,
when you now return to that spiritualist
to get more, he demanded for blood?
Yeah.
Okay, now tell us what was the amount that you
collected through this instant money?
And once again, what were the conditions attached?
How you would use this money,
and the things you could not use this money to do?
You know for the first person,
when the money comes, you would
go and deposit the money in a bank.
After which you will go and withdraw part of
the money and come give to him.
So for the second person, I went to him
and he also gave me his options.
And then I chose what I wanted.
He said that when the money comes,
I have to give 30 cedis out of it
to three virgins -
kids who are growing up,
before spending your money.
For them, virtually they will never
give birth in their entire life again.
I hope we understand what our brother just said.
So the condition attached was that you
had to give some of this money to three virgins.
And what would happen to those
girls once you gave them the money?
When I give them the money,
and they spend their money,
they will never give birth in the entire life.
Yes, I know most of my friends
were also engaged in all this.
He told me that it was my star that wanted
to give the money for the virgins.
Most of my friends that were also in this,
had their rules and what they had to do.
My friend for instance - his rule was,
when women have the menstruation
and then they throw their pads outside,
he pays people to go and pick them
and bring it to him
and then he will take you to the
ritualist for his star cleansing.
When a woman pad gets in there,
she will never give birth again.
There was no way she was going
to give birth in her entire life again.
Okay, so what our brother is
saying is that the spiritualist
would give different conditions
according to the person that came to
him before doing the money rituals.
In the case of our brother, when he
was given this instant money,
the condition was - he had to give a certain amount of
this money to three virgin girls.
And whoever collected that
money, once they spent it -
they would never be able to
give birth again in their life.
And other friends of his had conditions whereby.
If a woman dropped her menstruation pads somewhere
in a public place or on the floor,
he would pay someone to collect
those menstruation pads,
bring it to the ritualist and from that point forward
the person who dropped their menstruation pad
would never be able to have a child in their life.
So continue, brother. Tell us more about
your activities with these ritualists.
When I went with this to ritualists, they gave me options.
In Ghana we have people who run micro finances, savings and loan companies.
Most of the serving and loan companies that I knew
were also into this.
They also had their option, now they would go
for money from this people, then come to give as loan.
If you have a company or an asset and
you use it as a collateral to take that money
and you are not prayerful, forget it!
That asset that you used as
a collateral become a liability.
There was no way you could pay
that money back.
So then eventually your assets become theirs.
So just to explain more about how you
would do this spiritual transaction with the bank
to deceive people to do a loan.
Just explained very clearly to
people how you would go about it.
With a bank issue, they would charm
the money for you.
Let me talk about the savings and loan aspect.
Now you go to him for a loan.
He would take your assets,
something valuable that would be
more than the money you are taking as a collateral.
And then he will give you the money you want.
Now, if you are a good Christian, someone who prays,
forget! There was no way you could pay the money back.
So then what you used as a
collateral will eventually becomes his
because you can't pay the money back.
When this money comes, you
will be asked to deposit it in a bank.
When you deposit the money into the bank,
the bank will mix it with your money,
and then you go for a fresh money,
and if, let's say, the owner of the bank,
the managerial part of the bank are not prayerful,
they would face crisis in their banking business
because their money is going to go in a drain.
Because what I was made to know -
the spirit that gave the money, was from the sea.
So when they come out there,
mix their money with our money,
then they drain the money back
to the sea.
So they keep it there so when
someone goes to them for money,
they can get the money and
give to the person.
So when these money started coming up,
I started drinking, smoking, I was on drugs,
womanizing, clubbing, all sort of ungodly things.
First academically l was good, but when
I started involving myself in this situation
I came down, I fell totally.
My dad was someone who was so
strict, when it comes to academics.
Before you go ahead. You talked
about the lifestyle
you were living. Can you just explain
more about
all this money you were receiving from
the ritualist - ritual money?
What were you using it for, if you can't explain more?
Like you said, you drink, smoke
- how much were you smoking?
What were you drinking?
How much drugs were you taking?
For people to understand,
how you were wasting this money.
I could take about 22 - 23 packets
of cigarettes within a day.
I drank bottles of vodka.
I was on drugs - high drugs, cocaine, weed.
I was also on pills.
I would go out there in club,
I would blow money, throw money on air.
People would see that I was around.
Anywhere I found myself, I wanted
my present to be felt by people.
Because I was getting money, I could
command money anytime I wanted.
So that was the kind of lifestyle I was living.
So the money you received from this ritualists,
you could only use it for devilish purposes.
You could never use it for anything that would help you,
benefit you or glorify God?
When you start using this money,
the mindset won't come, that you
should use it to do something good.
I was the type, any place I found myself -
as I said earlier on - I easily made friends.
Yet when someone told me he has a problem,
I feel pity for the person, but knowing
where the money is coming from,
I just didn't want to give that money to the person.
So I used to earn monthly income from my dad.
So when that money comes, I would give that
money to the people who need
money from me
and then I would be spending the
money that I commanding.
Yeah, that was what I was doing.
There was times in school,
I started giving loans to people.
When a person comes to me and tells me his problem,
I would ask you why you need the money.
If, let's say, your problem is kind of family problem
and you need money and stuff,
willingly I will give you the loan
from the money my dad gave me
and you won't pay back.
But when you say you want to use it for clubbing,
and I know you, you have been clubbing -
then you are in trouble.
I would take your laptop, something bigger than
the amount I want to give you.
I would sell it that day because I knew
you can't pay the money back.
There was no way you can pay the money back.
So I would give you a loan and sell that day.
Even if I give you three years to
pay the money, you can't pay back.
So I hope we are listening to our brother saying
that because the source of the money he was receiving
was demonic and devilish, he never had
the mindset to use it for anything good.
He couldn't use it to help people.
He couldn't use it to give to people.
He could only use it for things such as clubbing, drinking,
womanizing and taking drugs.
He said he was smoking up to 20
packets of cigarettes in a single day
as a result of all of this money he was using.
And tell us, how did this affect you in terms of your
education and your life generally?
From onset I was good academically;
my dad was someone who is so
strict when it came to academics.
So I was so good, but I when I started entangling
myself with this kind of ungodly acts,
my academics fell.
I went back to the spiritualist and told
him that my academics has gone down.
So he gave me a concoction which
I used to bath with at midnight.
And took some each time I wanted to study.
When I took that stuff, I realized that
everything I studied, stuck in my head.
Brother, you mentioned earlier
that the first ritualist you went to,
initially they did not demand for blood but later on
they started demanding for blood. Now tell us,
when this witchdoctor demanded for blood,
what was your reaction?
What did you do thereafter?
Personally, I've been to about five witchdoctors -
each time they demanded for blood, I would insult them.
I would tell them that from the onset,
they told me that there was no blood.
There was a time I was attacked
physically - I would see them in my dreams.
There was a time I saw one physically
threatening that I have spent his money
and it was time for me to give him something,
and I was refusing so he was going
to kill me.
The next day I took a phone, I
called him and I insulted him,
then I moved to a different spiritualist.
So each time they tried doing
something, I would just insult them.
You mentioned as well... We're just
asking these questions
for us to learn so we too can identify
what's been happening in society
in our lives,
so we can be careful and conscious of it.
You mentioned that there were
different types of money
that the ritualist offered you -
that your own in your own case
you demanded for 'instant money'.
What were the other options that he gave you,
and tell us more about what they involved.
As I said from the onset, there was
the 'wallet money'.
In the 'wallet money', they
will command money for you.
For example, if you are in Nigeria they
will command 1000 Naira for you.
That is the highest denomination, they
will command it for you.
Then you go outside there and buy something,
for example, 100 naira out of 1000 naira.
The storekeeper will give exchange of 900 Naira.
Now you will put the 900 naira somewhere separately
and you put the wallets that you sent
to the spiritualist back into your pocket.
Thirty seconds later, the thousand naira that you used in purchasing
the stuff from the shop would
come back into your wallet.
So depending on number of shops
you go within a day,
that will determine the amount
of money you get within a day.
The storekeepers who trade -
if that money mix with your money,
and you're not someone who so prayerful,
forget it! The maximum you can go is six month -
you can't account for your money.
The second one was the 'bank money'.
That one, will come. You just send it to your bank.
To store it in a bank, now the bank
will mix that money
with their money and then when you
are going to withdraw
normally you have to wait for like three weeks
that is the kind of condition.
When you deposit the money in the bank,
you wait for three weeks.
After three weeks you can go
to the bank and withdraw the money.
When you go and withdraw the money,
you know banks give loans and stuff.
So they might have used your money
to give a loan to someone
or they might have mixed it with your money.
Now you go for fresh money.
One thing I realized after I was delivered
was that these spiritualists when
they charm the money for you,
they would never use a dime of that money.
They would tell you to go and send it to bank
or go and use it after which you come and thank them.
They would never spend that money, so we have to take
the money outside and bring a fresh money to them,
before they will spend it.
So the bank will mix with your money, and then you
also go and withdraw money from the bank.
So that different money would
come which you can send to the ritualist to spend.
If the managerial board of the bank are not God fearing,
people who know God,
they are going to face crisis in their business.
So you mean to say that there are many people
right now who because they are not prayerful,
God-fearing, they're facing collapses in their business,
in their in their entire lives as a result of this ritual money
that people like yourself were involving
yourselves in before your deliverance?
Yes, so after the first ritualist,
I was compelled to go for a different one.
But I didn't know how to get the money,
so I came home, picked my mum's fridge,
my mum's stuffs.
I went out there and sold them, just to get money.
So I wanted some money from my dad,
and he told me that unless I come here,
there was no way he was going
to give me that money.
I agreed, I had an aunt who was having a leg problem
and she was also coming here,
and I agreed to come with her.
Now, before you get to the point of coming here,
what was your impression about
this ministry before you came here?
Did you use to watch Emmanuel TV,
or what was your reaction to
Emmanuel TV before you came here?
My Uncle, I have an uncle who is in Ghana,
he used to watch Emmanuel TV a lot.
So he was the one I was staying with.
Each time I was on vacation and I go home,
I would make sure I create a problem.
I would create a confusion between my uncle and I,
then I would be asked to move and
go to stay with my aunt.
When I move to my aunts place,
she doesn't watch Emmanuel TV,
so am always free there.
There were times I could cause problem
and I would be asked to go and
stay with my grandmother.
At her place, my uncle has bought
her satellite for her - a decoder.
So she always watches Emmanuel TV.
She's old.
So I would say: "Okay". When she is there...
You know, when you change the channel she would be angry.
So I would go to the back of the decoder
and I would remove the cables of the decoder,
and then I would tell her the station has gone off.
And she would ask, "Really?"
and I would confirm, "Yes."
And she would go and sleep.
When she goes to her room, I would fix the cable back,
and watch the channel I want to watch.
So you hated Emanuel TV before coming here?
Yes! I really didn't like it. Yeah.
You know, each time I watched it,
I just felt tormented.
Our brother is saying that he went
to the extent that he would actually
physically go and unplug the decoder in his grandmother's
house to stop her from watching Emmanuel TV
so he could watch what he wanted -
because anytime he watched Emmanuel TV,
he didn't feel comfortable,
he felt something tormenting him.
So tell us, what led to your actually being here, in the
Synagogue Church of all Nations?
Before I move to that, you know
most of these spiritualists
I was talking about - they used to
advertise on television.
So there was a particular station that they used to advertise - that was
the station that I liked watching.
So I would make my grandmother
to go and sleep
and then I would put the channel.
So I would watch.
Then I would pick my numbers
and my things from there.
As I was saying, I wanted some money from my dad.
It got to a time I began to extort money from people.
I would take money from people, I was into fraud,
I would fraud people and take their money.
So I wanted to take money from my
dad to add to my money,
so that I would go to a different spiritualist
because the previous one had
asked for blood and I blasted him.
So I wanted to go for a different one.
So my dad told me that if I didn't come
to the Synagogue Church of all Nations,
there was no way he was going to get that money.
I had an aunt who was also having a leg injury.
So I was like: "Ok, I will come with these people,
and when I come, we would end up
in the overflow congregation,
and the wisemen would come
around and touch her and go home.
And I would go and tell my dad that I was
here because my aunt will testify that I was here."
So that the money I wanted would be given to me.
We went there and the foreigners were
asked to go to a different room.
So that they would start sharing
the pass to enter the auditorium.
When we went there, I swapped the pass three times.
First, I saw it sharing to my raw, I left my raw
and I went to sit in a different place.
They started coming again, I left
there and I went to sit outside.
I was sitting outside, and then
they came there again.
I was running away and the
guy placed the pass into my hand.
Because my aunties were watching
me, they were suspecting something.
So I just followed them.
We came and sat among the
congregation at the back there.
I thought that my aunt will be touched and she would go
and I would go and get my money.
When I was sitting there I wasn't
concentrating with what was happening here.
I was just thinking how I was going to get the money
and do my stuff at home.
So I was sitting there and it was testimony time.
And I saw a friend of mine here giving
testimony about this same problem.
I was sited there and I thought,
"Jesus Christ, this guy has been caught,
I will be the next victim."
So I had to run away because I was not safe.
So you mean the brother that gave his testimony
last week about being delivered
from the spirit of stealing -
you knew him personally that
you were both involved act.
Yes, I knew him personally.
I tried going out,
but then the ushers at the entrance
couldn't allow me to go out.
I told them that I want to go and
urinate but they refused.
So I came back and sat down,
I was sitting down when the man of God
entered the auditorium.
Immediately he entered the auditorium
I started sweating,
I was feeling headache,
I said I was going out, the usher told me
since the man of God was inside, there was no way,
they were not going to allow me to go out.
I asked, "What kind of nonsense was that?
I came in myself and I want to go out
and you are telling me not to go out?"
I really pushed but they didn't allow me to go out.
So I came and sit down. Each time the man of God
came that way, I bend down my face.
When the man of God was on stage,
there was a man of war on stage.
It was a man who stood up.
And then the man of God delivered him,
he was from my lane.
When he stood up, I thought, "What
kind of nonsense is this?"
Won't you see you made this man
to come to this area and I will be caught.
In fact when I was sitting down,
I knew mine has come.
So I needed way to run away.
So I said, "What nonsense is
this? Won't you sit down? I will be caught."
I was praying and saying, "I pray this
man of God won't come here."
Fortunately or unfortunately for me,
he didn't come to the other lane.
He was at the other lane
and he left, I said, "Thank God."
The wise men started going round. It was prayer time.
They touched my aunt, she was not close to me.
She was at the far end and I was in a different place.
They touched her, I thanked
God they have touched her.
So I was coming to move from
where I was sitting
and go and mix with the people
they have already touched.
So that they won't touch me, since my aunt has
been touched, you would think I
was also touched.
There were three lanes to the
place that I was sitting, I felt slaps.
I felt three strong slaps.
There were three guys before me at the far end.
I was seeing him as a human being
but then when he got closer to
me, I was seeing fire.
I wanted to run away, but the guys had hold
me so stiff that I couldn't run away.
I realized that I was on the floor,
and I was asked to rise up.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So brother, just describe again as the wiseman
approached you, when you were trying to leave the place -
you said you felt something slap you.
Just describe exactly what happened at that moment.
I felt a slap from behind.
I turned like this and another one came.
I was wondering because I have been through prayers.
My parents have taken me through pastors.
I would go there with a problem, the next thing they
would tell me that I was coming to travel abroad.
I should go and bring money.
I would feel happy that I was traveling abroad,
so I would go and bring the money.
But I realized since I came, sitting
down there and I started feeling slaps.
I thought, "This place wasn't safe for me,
I thought it was, so I have to go."
All the ways that I was trying to escape was not helping.
The ushers were on my neck.
They just didn't want me to go out.
So when the wiseman came
closer, another slap came.
I thought, "Today I have been caught."
I told myself - the end has come!
Because if my friend was standing here
testifying, my end has come.
I just saw fire.
The fire was so intense
that I tried running away,
but the ushers held me so tight.
I couldn't do anything.
Then I realized I was on the floor,
and I was asked to rise up.
One more time, people of God,
let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
So brother, it has been one week now since
your deliverance. By the grace of God you've been here, in
the Synagogue Church of all Nations
and spending time in God's presence.
Just tell us what is the transformation in your life
ever since your deliverance?
Last week since I have been here,
I've not been on any alcohol.
I've not been on any drug.
I feel revealed, all the thoughts I was
having in my head - they are all gone.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So right now, as you're standing here,
what can you say about going to ritualists,
getting money - quick money,
instant money - through demonic means?
I mean now, you're standing here,
you've been delivered. What do
you want to say about such issues?
You know, in life
we all have different track race,
we didn't start at the same time.
Let's say, someone probably may
have committed series of abortion,
but immediately she gets married
she gets pregnant instantly.
But a virgin also waits centuries
after she would give birth.
Someone who completes university at the age of 20,
and she has to wait home for like five
years before he gets employment.
Someone who also completes at age
25 immediately get employment.
I've realized that we all don't have the same track
and our finish lines are not the same.
Now, with this devilish thing the
devil will never give you something
without taking something back from you.
If he doesn't take it in kind, he is
going to take it physically.
It's either your money,
your child or something that you cherish.
And mostly when they are coming, they come for something you cherish most.
That is what I realized.
Because they realized, let's say,
I like kids. I was playing with kids,
I like helping people, they would ask me to give money,
out of the money they would
charm for me to virgins - which are kids.
So eventually like playing with kids,
they will use those kids that I like playing
with as a source or kind of to satisfy their gods.
I realized also in life although you might
be going through challenges, the ups and downs in life,
bu it is not the end.
The devil will give you something to sustain you,
but he would never give you a solution.
It's only the Lord Jesus Christ that
can give you the final solution
that can release you from all your entangles,
that can release you from your case.
It's only the Lord Jesus Christ
that can help you.
With this Emmanuel TV and the anointing water and the anointed sticker.
It is real.
First, I was a critic, my people would be using it and I would tell them not to use it.
There were times I could go to
church and intentionally fall
for the people around me to think that I am delivered,
so that when I go to ask for money they would give me.
So when they touched me, I would pretend and fall
but here I wasn't touched.
In fact, I wasn't touched, I just fall -
I don't know what happened.
So there is God here, so if you
come here,
believing there is God here,
trust me - you are going to be
delivered in Jesus' name.
Amen, let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ
for our brother's wonderful deliverance.
So just a final question for our brother.
Now,
that Jesus Christ has delivered you -
what do you want to say to people outside
there, who are still involving themselves
in money rituals,
and visiting spiritualists, witchdoctors, herbalists?
What do you want to say to them?
My advice to these people is:
now, that I have been delivered,
I hope that Lord Jesus Christ has delivered
all those girls that I used to give money to
out of the hands of the devil.
My advice first goes to parents out there.
If someone starts giving your kid money,
you should question where the
person is getting the money from.
Secondly, it goes to women out there.
Please, when you have your menstruation,
please dig a hole or find a way
of disposing your menstrual pads.
And then also to my friends out there,
to the big men and the big guys that I met.
I know some of them might be watching me.
I met them, when I was going to
the spiritualist for my help.
They should all come to Jesus Christ.
Because there is no final solution
than in the house of the Lord.
Because we've tried it and I have moved steps
but then I've realized that with all this spiritualists,
they all have their rules.
These rules are never the same.
But I have realized with our Jesus Christ His rule is one.
The Bible is only one.
There is no Bible that is going to come after
and there is no Bible that came before.
But then with all these spiritualists - they all use
different books and they all have their rules.
So we should all stick to one rule.
Which is the rule of our Lord Jesus Christ.
They should all come for deliverance,
and I hope that the Lord Jesus Christ
who delivered me out of this bondage,
would take them all out in Jesus' name.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So I hope we understood what our
brother said there. Now, that he is delivered,
he knows that all of those virgin
girls that was giving money to -
and as a result of that would lose
their menstruation
and would never be able to have a child -
he says that they too are delivered and
all the people who have touched this
ritual money that he was involved in through his deliverance -
God has touched them and delivered them as well.
And finally, brother, you said that
you've been involved in this from
the age of eight. How old are you right now?
I'm 20 years old.
So you can just imagine how at
this young age of our brother,
satan has really been using him,
but we thank Jesus Christ that today
he is delivered and we give all the
glory to our Lord Jesus Christ.
We pray that God will give you the
grace to maintain this deliverance
so that what you've received will stand
the test of time in Jesus' name.
We believe you have been inspired
by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more
of God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up to date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives,
Changing nations and Changing the world
TT: Liz
RV: PavelTatyanaZheleznyakov 20/07/2018